indyarocks.com 2011-12-13

# Indyarocks - Privacy Policy

  | **About Indyarocks.com**  
  | Indyarocks.com is an online and mobile centric service that allows members to build and leverage their network of contacts in incredibly powerful ways. Indyarocks.com is designed to facilitate networking, media-sharing amongst people within the network and as such encourages the disclosure of personal information by members to fully leverage the powerful features of Indyarocks.com

The disclosure of personal information is always a sensitive issue and the Indyarocks team takes it very seriously. We consider it our highest priority to protect the privacy of our members. To that end this privacy policy outlines the types of information Indyarocks.com collects and how that information is used in the operation of the site. We understand you may not want everyone in the world-removeto have the information you share on Indyarocks.com. Therefore, we give you control of your information. Use the Privacy Setting options available to manage how and with whom you want to share your information.   
  
  | **Information collection and use by Indyarocks.com**  
  | Indyarocks.com collects user information such as Email, Name, Age, Mobile Number and other such information to authenticate users as well as to send Email and Mobile notifications relating to the users activity on the site. Indyarocks also collects other kinds of profile data which will assist members in networking, communicating and sharing with each other. Every member is also given adequate options to limit the sharing of their personal information with other members. Except for your email address, First name, Last name, Age, and Mobile Number, Indyarocks doesn’t mandate any other personal information. All the other information submission is left to the members’ discretion. If we are asking for any unwarranted information then please let us know.

Non-personally-identifiable information may or may not be collected by Indyarocks for managing and improving website and to track usage of members.

Some information that might not be viewable by other members (like first name, last name, email address), can be used for search purposes. While a member might be searchable- based on an email, the results will not display-add any restricted personal information. Members' Display Picture, Profile Data and other information only facilitate networking and communicating with other members.

Notifications from Indyarocks, to-add a member’s email address or Mobile Phone can be controlled by the member through the account setting page.

Indyarocks.com or  its partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on Indyarocks.com. During this time, they may ask members’ to provide personal information including name, email address and/or home address or to answer questions on the website. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested information from. It will be clear at the point of collection, who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.  
  
  | **Communication with Non-members**  
  |   
Indyarocks members can send invitations to friends to join Indyarocks via our automated invitation system. [Indyarocks.com](http://ndyarocks.com/) may or may not store the email addresses that members provide to enable the respondents to be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. Indyarocks.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations or auto-reminders. Recipients of invitations from Indyarocks.com may contact [indyarocks.com](http://indyarocks.com/) through [privacy@indyarocks.com](mailto:privacy@indyarocks.com) to request the removal of their information from our database.  
  | **Use of Cookies**  
  | Indyarocks.com may use cookies to store visitor information. The information stored will be used to provide enhanced experience for the user. This information will not be linked to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept /reject all or some cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set.Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences; however, you must enable cookies from Indyarocks.com in order to use some functions on the site.  
  | **Third Party Links**  
  | Indyarocks.com may contain links to third party websites. Indyarocks.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Indyarocks.com.   
  | **Chat Rooms, Online Personal Diary and Blogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums**  
  | We urge you to be aware of information you voluntarily post on to Blogs, Graffiti Walls, My Life, Forums, Comments, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums. Such information can be accessed by the public and can be used to send you unsolicited communications.  
  | **Editing or Removing Information**  
  | Indyarocks.com members have the complete flexibility to modify / remove their information. However, certain information like your email address and  username  will not be modifiable for the functionality of the site. However, a member will be able to delete his/her profile completely. If for any reason you wish to remove some information and have difficulty in doing so please contact us on – privacy[@][indyarocks.com](http://indyarocks.com/)  
  | **Email and SMS Choice/Opt-out**  
  |  If a member chooses not to receive any notification emails or SMS, he/she can opt out of the service (through-remove) (by-add) changing the settings in the “Account Setting” page under Edit Profile.  
  | **Third Party Advertising**  
  | Ads can be of two kinds - (1) Those that belong to Indyarocks.com, or  (2) Those that belong to third party advertisers. The third party advertisers may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about whether you, or others who are using your computer, viewed their advertisements and determine which ads were clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Indyarocks.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party advertisers.  
  | **Security**  
  | Indyarocks.com has implemented security measures to protect member information from loss, misuse and alteration. Each of our employees is aware of our security policies, and your information is only available to those employees who need it to perform their jobs. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.   
  | **Sharing and Disclosure of Information Indyarocks.com Collects**  
  | Except as otherwise stated in this privacy statement, Indyarocks.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Indyarocks.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Indyarocks.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. 

Indyarocks.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Indyarocks.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.  
  
  | **Changes in our Privacy**  
  | Please be aware that with changing legal and moral practices, Indyarocks.com may change its Privacy Policy. We will do our best to ensure you are aware of any changes in the privacy policy. We request you  to refer to-add this section frequently for updates, if any.  
  |    
  |    
  | Your Team   
@Indyarocks   
Let’s Celebrate Life  
  |    
  |
